<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Video Dessert Rice Coconut on The Ulampinoy Project</title>
    <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/categories/video-dessert-rice-coconut/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Video Dessert Rice Coconut on The Ulampinoy Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.ulampinoy.com/categories/video-dessert-rice-coconut/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Palitaw</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/palitaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/palitaw/</guid>
      <description> Classic Pinoy dessert of rice cakes topped with shredded coconut, sugar and sesame seeds.
INGREDIENTS  1 coconut, finely shredded 1 cup white sugar 30 grams sesame seeds, toasted 400 grams glutinous rice flour (galapong) 1 1&amp;frasl;2 cup water, for the dough 1 big pot of boiling water for cooking the rice cakes   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork Siomai</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-siomai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-siomai/</guid>
      <description>Siomai is the Philippines most popular dim sum. You can find it everywhere – from the tiniest streets to the mega malls. Siomai is easily the fastest merienda or even an ulam option. It has the perfect combination of pork and spicy dip (saw-sawan).
Siomai comes in different varieties and flavor mutations but we love the classic and simple pork siomai.
Ingredients  1&amp;frasl;2 kg ground pork 1 medium carrot, grated 1 medium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork Ribs Adobo</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-ribs-adobo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-ribs-adobo/</guid>
      <description> Pork ribs adobo with potatoes
INGREDIENTS  1 kg pork spare ribs, cut in small portions 2-3 medium potatoes, cut into cubes 1 head of garlic. peeled 2 bay leaves (dahon ng laurel) 1 tablespoon black peppercorns (pamintang buo) 1&amp;frasl;2 cup soy sauce 1 cup water 1&amp;frasl;2 cup cooking oil for frying the potatoes   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>