<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Ulampinoy Project</title>
    <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Ulampinoy Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 23:57:11 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.ulampinoy.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>La Bahia</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/post/la-bahia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 23:57:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/post/la-bahia/</guid>
      <description>Mga ilan taon na rin ang nakalipas mula nang i-rekomenda sa amin ng ilang kaibigan ang La Bahia. Ang kanilang mga noodle soup at sariling-gawang mga dumplings ang una naming sinubukan at nagustuhan. Mula noon ay lagi na namin itong binabalik-balikan!
 Noodle soup na parehong napakasarap: seafoods at beef   Sa weekend kapag nagagawi kami sa Tetuán at doon inaabutan ng pananghalian, isa sa pangunahing pinagpipilian namin ay ang la Bahia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agahang Kastila</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/post/agahang-kastila/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 23:30:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/post/agahang-kastila/</guid>
      <description>Ang tipikal na agahang Kastila ay kalimitang magaang lang. Nariyan ang ikonikong Churros.
 Churros and Freshly-squeezed Orange Juice   Tinapay na tinusta at pinahiran ng olive oil, at giniling na kamatis at binudburan ng kaunting asin  Tostada de tomate   Parque del Buen Retiro Pagkatapos ng masarap na almusal, kami ay namasyal sa parke. At sari&amp;rsquo;t-saring bagay ang sa ami&amp;rsquo;y naghihintay.
 Madrid Book Festival sa Retiro Park    Author book signing    Quartet band playing in Retiro Park    Isa sa mga natatanging gusali sa loob ng parke ay ang Palacio de Cristal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laing ni Popeye</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/post/weekly-laing-mushroom-tomato/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 01:03:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/post/weekly-laing-mushroom-tomato/</guid>
      <description>Laing na yata ang pinakamasarap na ulam na gulay. Paano naman kasi: baboy at hipon ang sahog, gata ang sarsa at sili ang pampaliyab. Talaga namang mapaparami ka! 🍚
Alam nating lahat na dahon at tangkay ng gabi ang sangkap ng laing. Alam rin nating napakahirap humanap ng niyan dito sa Europa.
 &amp;ldquo;Necessity is the mother of invention&amp;rdquo;
 Kapit na kapit ang kasabihang iyan lalo na sa pagluluto at higit pa kapag matagal ka nang malayo sa Filipinas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mongolian Beef</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/mongolian-beef/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/mongolian-beef/</guid>
      <description>Napakasarap at madaling lutuing beef stir-fry na saktong-sakto ulam.
BEEF at MARINADE:  1 kg. beef 2 buong bawang (12-15 butil) 4 tbs. Chinese cooking wine 3&amp;frasl;4 cornstarch 1 tb. baking soda 1 itlog pamintang durog 1 L cooking oil para sa pritong-lubog (deep-fry)  SAUCE:  1&amp;frasl;2 cup soy sauce 3 tbs. mirin 1&amp;frasl;4 cup sugar  GARNISH:  Green onion Roasted sesame seeds  Kain na! At huwag mag-atubiling mag-subscribe at paki-share ang ulam Pinoy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monggo</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/monggo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/monggo/</guid>
      <description> Ang monggo ay isang masarap na ulam na kadalasang may katambal na pritong isda. Karaniwang malunggay o talbos ng ampalaya ang sinasamang gulay. Napakasarap rin ng sasahugan pa ng tinapá at chicharon!
INGREDIENTS:  Monggo Liempo ng baboy Bawang Sibuyas Ampalaya Dahon ng spinach Patis at asin Siling haba Tubig  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paksiw na Bangus, Ginisang Upo at Vino de Madrid</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/post/weekend-bits-03-paksiw-na-bangus-ginisang-upo-vino-madrid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 22:17:48 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/post/weekend-bits-03-paksiw-na-bangus-ginisang-upo-vino-madrid/</guid>
      <description>Madalang lang makatagpo at limitado ang bangus dito sa Europa, kaya naman kung makabili kami, imbes na basta i-prito lang, niluluto namin ito na mas tradisyonal hangga&amp;rsquo;t maari gaya ng paksiw.
 Paksiw na Bangus   ANG PAKSIW ay ang pagluluto sa sukà na may kasamang luya, bawang, sibuyas, at sili. Maasim ito gaya ng sinigang na bangus pero hindi ito masabaw. Ang paksiw ay lalo nang masarap kung lumamig na o kapag inulam sa kinabukasan pa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chistorra, Sinangag at Sunny Side Up Eggs</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/post/fried-rice-eggs-chistorra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 22:53:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/post/fried-rice-eggs-chistorra/</guid>
      <description>Long-si-log (longganisa, sinangag at itlog). Tap-si siyempre ang hari ng lahat ng mga si-log. Talagang mabigat ang agahang Pinoy. Kape ang katapat na panulak sa agahan.
May dalawang kampo ang almusal: Tinapay o kanin. Kung tinapay ang pili mo, pandesal o tasty bread ang hanap mo sa umaga. Pero kung ang kategorya mo ay kanin, ito ang tipo mong almusal. Kaya naman dinagdagan mo ang sinaing kagabi para may matirang kanin para sa sinangag sa kinaumagahan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turon, Kutsinta, atbp.</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/post/weekend-bits-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2016 21:08:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/post/weekend-bits-02/</guid>
      <description>Piknik sa parke kasama ng mga kaibigan. Kapag nagkayayaan, kahit biglaan lang, napakarami pa ring pagkain! Eh di ma-imagine mo na kung may patiunang abiso at preparasyon pa.
Ang weekend ay laging espesyal kasama ng mga barkada. Pahinga sa nakakapagod na rutin sa trahaho, hingahan ng niloob, biruan, tawanan&amp;hellip;
 Kainan sa parke   Halos lahat may dala kahit na ano lang, basta nabulungan mo na may get together, tiyak may bitbit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kesong Kambing, Talong Pickle at Alamang</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/post/weekend-bits-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2016 22:59:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/post/weekend-bits-01/</guid>
      <description>Excited kaming i-launch ngayon ang kauna-unahang edisyon ng Weekend Bits. Sari-sari at random na weekend adventure.
Nitong nakaraang Linggo sa aming lingguhang pamimili ng supply para sa darating na linggo, kami&amp;rsquo;y dumaan sa Carrefour at may naghihintay na sorpresa.
 Buháy na talangka   Napakadalang na merong buháy na talangkang mabibili dito sa Madrid. Kung meron mang buháy ay naghihingalo na! At nang mailuto mataba at punó ng aligi ang bawat isa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ulampinoy 2016</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/ulampinoy-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 20:59:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/ulampinoy-2016/</guid>
      <description>Masaya kaming ibalita sa inyo ang launch ng bagong disenyo ng Ulampinoy. Maraming improvements ang aming ginawa base sa mga feedback na tinanggap namin mula sa inyong lahat.
Ipinasya rin namin na i-publish ito sa wikang Tagalog. Nais naming i-share sa inyo ang mga recipe at iba pang bagay sa paraang mas personal na para bang panauhin namin kayo o panauhin ninyo kami sa inyong tahanan. Nakatitiyak kaming mas makulay ang ating kuwentuhan kung ito ay sa wikang Pilipino.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Ulampinoy</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/top-10-ulampinoy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 20:59:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/top-10-ulampinoy/</guid>
      <description>Tiyak na ang bawat isa ay may kani-kaniyang listahan ng mga paboritong ulam Pinoy. Narito ang ang aming top 10:
Adobong Manok Lahat malamang ay sasangayon na adobo ang #1 sa mga putaheng Pinoy, at puede sigurong ipalagay na adobong manok ang #1 sa lahat ng abodo dahil mas madaling makabili ng manok, kasi naman, mas mura ang manok kaysa baboy.
Adobong Baboy Ito sana ang #1 kaya lang mas mahal ang baboy kaysa manok!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pancit Bihon</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/pancit-bihon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 20:25:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/pancit-bihon/</guid>
      <description>Ano pa ang mas Pinoy sa pancit? Sa handaan o mga kainan, ang pancit ang isa sa mga pinaka-popular na pagkaing Filipino. Gaya ng adobo, napakaraming klase ng pancit. Pero ang pancit bihon ang isa sa aming paborito!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>La Bahia&#39;s Tasty Noodle Soup</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2016-01-21-la-bahia-noodle-soups/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 20:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2016-01-21-la-bahia-noodle-soups/</guid>
      <description>Two years ago, our friends recommended a really good Chinese restaurant that make some really tasty noodle soup. It was truly savoury!
 Bowls of tasty Chinese beef and seafoods noodle soup   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smashing Barcelona</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2016-01-05-smashing-barcelona/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 20:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2016-01-05-smashing-barcelona/</guid>
      <description>I was sent to Barcelona last October 2015 to attend the Smashing Conference. It was a great fun experience! Although it was my fifth visit, there are always new things and places to discover in Barcelona.
The conference venue was the magnificent Palau de la Música Catalana. The grandoise ceiling (shown above), stained-glass works and all the details are just splendid.
 Magnifecent Palau de la Música Catalana Facade and Terrace   During lunch breaks the attendees were encouraged to roam around the block close to the venue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burger Steak Rice</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-08-20-beef-burger-steak-rice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-08-20-beef-burger-steak-rice/</guid>
      <description>We love burgers! If you have meat between those buns why not with rice? And if it has to be a rice topping it needs to have sarsa (sauce). This is why burger steak is a perfect ulam!
The burger patties were prepared with a bit more of spices than the usual for hamburgers. It is loaded with garlic and a loads of ground black pepper. Adding up these will make it more connected as a rice topping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Togue Young Corn Stir-Fry</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-08-05-togue-young-corn-stir-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-08-05-togue-young-corn-stir-fry/</guid>
      <description>Hey there! We are back making and eating delicious home cooked meals. We have some upcoming news that will help spread the Ulampinoy love.
Meanwhile, enjoy the tasty and healthy bean sprout with young corn stir-fry. Makes a great take-away lunch. Try this: add a bit of kick with a dash of grounded cayenne pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Currently, cooking…</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-08-03-ulampinoy-dos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 23:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-08-03-ulampinoy-dos/</guid>
      <description>We are glad to launch today the fresh new look of UlamPinoy. We are currently redesigning the entire UlamPinoy site to make your visits to UlamPinoy fun and worthwhile an experience no matter if you are hunting for some tasty recipes or just feasting your eyes with our food adventure collections.
 Bowl of beef brisket noodle soup   As the title above suggests it is a work in progress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sinigang na Bangus</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-07-02-sinigang-bangus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2015 22:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-07-02-sinigang-bangus/</guid>
      <description>Milkfish or bangus is cooked in tamarind-based broth with onions, ginger, tomatoes, green chilis and pechay. Sinigang na Bangus is very popular because milkfish is the most common farmed fish in the Philippines. But not all bangus are equal! The most sought after is Dagupan Bangus in the province of Pangasinan.
 One whole tomato   Whether you are using the real sampaloc or the instant powder version, adding tomato to your sinigang upscale the broth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jamón Tumaca</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-07-01-tumaca/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-07-01-tumaca/</guid>
      <description>Typical Spaniard breakfast of toasted bread with jamón, tomato(finely chopped or grated) and extra-virgin olive oil.
 Pan tostada con tomate   Upscale it by adding a top layer of cured Spanish ham. When I said Spanish ham, I mean this:
 Charcutería, the one stop shop for everything pork goodness. All made possible with Spain&amp;rsquo;s super dry low air humidity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Churros &amp; Chocolate</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-06-26-churros-chocolate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2015 18:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-06-26-churros-chocolate/</guid>
      <description>Freshly made churros sprinkled with sugar and hot chocolate dip at the local churrería. It was both delightful eat and watch how it was made.
 La Churrera, the amazing churros machine   Kneading the dough, la masa, and the churros-making machine &amp;mdash; La Churrera
 Skillful skimming and draining   Churros ready! Skimmed and drained from the hot oil with the help of a steel rod
 Empty plastic jars for chocolate dip to go   Churrería Art – empty plastic jars of chocolate if you are buying for to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monggo</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-06-26-monggo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2015 18:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-06-26-monggo/</guid>
      <description>Ginisang Monggo, the comfort food for all seasons. This I can have this every week. Paired with pritong isda or paksiw na isda is even better.
 Ginisang monggo on top of steamed rice   Quick tip: One of the essential step for the recipe is pre-cooking the mung beans by boiling until the skin of the beans separate. You don&amp;rsquo;t have to throw it.
 Pre-cooking to peel of skin   Check out our video recipe on how to cook Ginisang Monggo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kimchi</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-01-03-kimchi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2015 22:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-01-03-kimchi/</guid>
      <description>Spicy and sour are the flavors that could compliment any dish and enhance your appetite. Kimchi is both, spicy and sour.
It&amp;rsquo;s not easy to find a good kimchi here in Madrid. The bottled kimchi available at the Chinese store taste sweet! Really? Sweet kimchi? No thanks!
We found a proper Korean store in the Mercado de Maravillas in Cuatro Caminos. The shopkeeper is a Korean lady making her own kimchi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Misua and Patola</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2014-08-13-misua-patola/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2014-08-13-misua-patola/</guid>
      <description>Rice noodle (misua) soup with patola (luffa) and crispy pork belly strips
 Misua noodle soup with luffa   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beef Caldereta</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/beef-caldereta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/beef-caldereta/</guid>
      <description> Beef caldereta is one those dishes other than in the food shops that you can have only in a special meal (handaan).
INGREDIENTS:  Beef chunks Tomatoes, red and ripe Pineapple, chunks and juice from the can Liver spread, small can Potato and carrot Red and green sweet peppers Laurel leaves Salt and black pepper to taste Water  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Hot Spiced Vinegar</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/red-hot-spiced-vinegar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/red-hot-spiced-vinegar/</guid>
      <description> We&amp;rsquo;re back in the kitchen for the 3rd Season of UlamPinoy! For our first episode we are cooking a very popular Filipino vegetable stir-fry recipe – Chopsuey.
INGREDIENTS:  Beef chunks Tomatoes, red and ripe Pineapple, chunks and juice from the can Liver spread, small can Potato and carrot Red and green sweet peppers Laurel leaves Salt and black pepper to taste Water   Cooking chopsuey in a wok   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Afritada</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-afritada/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-afritada/</guid>
      <description>Easy to make one-pot chicken dish with vegetables. You can make a large batch and save some for your baon to work. It is a complete ulam where you have the sarsa for the rice and the main deal - chicken and vegetable.
Ingredients  Chicken Potatoes Carrots Red bell pepper Green bell pepper Tomatoes Garlic Onions Olive oil or canola Tomato sauce Patis (fish sauce) Salt and black pepper to taste   Cut into bite-size pieces   Procedure  Cut the chicken in medium portions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chopsuey</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chopsuey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chopsuey/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re back in the kitchen for the 3rd Season of UlamPinoy! For our first episode we are cooking a very popular Filipino vegetable stir-fry recipe – Chopsuey.
 Golden brown pork belly strips in a wok   Fast and easy to cook. Fire up the wok, brown the pork belly until golden and crispy. Mix in the chicken livers. Sauté garlic and onions with the pork and livers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Stir-fry</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-stir-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-stir-fry/</guid>
      <description> Fire up your wok and cook along with our easy to make chicken and vegetable stir-fry.
INGREDIENTS:  Chicken Vegetables   Red bell pepper on chopping board   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Sopas</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-sopas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-sopas/</guid>
      <description> Chicken and elbow macaroni soup cooked in milk as base with carrots, cabbage and sausage. Perfect comfort food during the cold winter days!
INGREDIENTS:  Chicken Elbow macaroni   Chicken Sopas served hot   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Crispy Pork Belly</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/super-crispy-pork-belly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/super-crispy-pork-belly/</guid>
      <description> Chicken and elbow macaroni soup cooked in milk as base with carrots, cabbage and sausage. Perfect comfort food during the cold winter days!
INGREDIENTS:  Beef chunks Tomatoes, red and ripe Pineapple, chunks and juice from the can Liver spread, small can Potato and carrot Red and green sweet peppers Laurel leaves Salt and black pepper to taste Water   Salt liberally the pork belly    Pork crackling with dip   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ginisang Green Beans</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/ginisang-green-beans/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/ginisang-green-beans/</guid>
      <description> Easy to cook sautéed green beans with crispy pork belly
INGREDIENTS:  Green beans Pork belly   Sauté the pork belly until golden brown    Covering while simmering tenderize the green beans faster   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revuelto de Setas</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/revuelto-setas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/revuelto-setas/</guid>
      <description> Simple to make Spanish omelette of mixed mushrooms and chorizo
INGREDIENTS:  Mushroom mix Eggs Spanish chorizo   Eggs dancing on a tray   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squid Adobo</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/squid-adobo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/squid-adobo/</guid>
      <description>Fresh squids cooked adobo style! We love it very much and it really shows – this is the second video of Adobong Pusit
 Preserve the ink duct if you buy the squid fresh or you can always use squid/cuttlefish ink sold in packets. Most supermarkets here in Madrid sell &amp;ldquo;tinta de sepia/calamar&amp;rdquo;
 Cuttlefish ink packet   Cook the squid at high heat in less time until it gets tender and add the vinegar for last.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garlic Pork Belly</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2013-10-23-garlic-pork-belly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2013-10-23-garlic-pork-belly/</guid>
      <description>Got some pork belly in your fridge? Easy to make yet delicious crispy pork belly strips.
 Fresh pork belly strips and cloves of garlic   Ingredients  1 kg pork belly (cut into thick strips) 1 head of garlic (cruched, peeled and chooped) 1&amp;frasl;2 cup vinegar 1&amp;frasl;2 cup water salt and black pepper to taste  Great with some fresh green salads
Here&amp;rsquo;s the video on how to cook this delicious recipe:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ginataang Kalabasa</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/ginataang-kalabasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/ginataang-kalabasa/</guid>
      <description> Squash, string beans and live crabs cooked in spiced coconut milk. Savoury and spicy!
INGREDIENTS:  Squash String beans Crabs   Long string beans bundle    Fresh kalabasa    Fresh from the market live crab   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crispy Garlic Pork Belly</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/garlic-pork-belly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/garlic-pork-belly/</guid>
      <description> Crispy, golden and garlicky pork belly
INGREDIENTS:  1 kg pork belly (cut into thick strips) 1 head of garlic (cruched, peeled and chooped) 1&amp;frasl;2 cup vinegar 1&amp;frasl;2 cup water salt and black pepper to taste   Fresh pork belly and handful of garlic cloves    Crispy garlic loaded liempo   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sinigang na Hipon at Isda</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/sinigang-hipon-isda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/sinigang-hipon-isda/</guid>
      <description> Seafoods stew of fish, shrimp, talbos ng kamote (sweet potato young leaves), tomatoes, ginger, mild green chili and onions.
INGREDIENTS:  1 kg pork belly (cut into thick strips) 1 head of garlic (cruched, peeled and chooped) 1&amp;frasl;2 cup vinegar 1&amp;frasl;2 cup water salt and black pepper to taste   Fresh sweet potato tops    Fresh sweet potato tops    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Tinola</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2013-10-07-chicken-tinola/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2013-10-07-chicken-tinola/</guid>
      <description>Tinola will be at the top the list of ulam na may sabaw. It is chicken broth soup with upo (bottle gourd), pechay (Chinese cabbage) and ginger.
Ingredients  Whole chicken, cut into portions Upo (bottle gourd), 1 medium cut into chunks Pechay (Chinese cabbage, bok choi is great alternative), stalks and leaves separated Mild long green chilis Ginger, peeled and sliced Garlic Onions Cooking oil Patis (fish sauce) Salt to taste  If you can get free-range chicken, the broth will be many times tastier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Tinola</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-tinola/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-tinola/</guid>
      <description> Savory and revitalizing chicken broth soup spiced with ginger, garlic, onions and with bottle gourd and pechay.
INGREDIENTS:  Whole chicken, 1 pc. cut into portions Upo (bottle gourd), 1 medium cut into chunks Pechay (Chinese cabbage, bok choi is great alternative), stalks and leaves separated Mild long green chilis Ginger, peeled and sliced Garlic Onions Cooking oil Patis (fish sauce) Salt to taste   Fresh chicken cuts    Fresh pechay    Bottle gourd gives the broth a sublte sweetness    It&amp;#39;s in the broth   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chopsuey</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2013-09-30-chopsuey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2013-09-30-chopsuey/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re back in the kitchen for the 3rd Season of UlamPinoy! For our first episode we are cooking a very popular Filipino vegetable stir-fry recipe – Chopsuey.
 Golden brown pork belly strips in a wok   Fast and easy to cook. Fire up the wok, brown the pork belly until golden and crispy. Mix in the chicken livers. Sauté garlic and onions with the pork and livers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tupperlicious – Adobo &amp; Laing</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2013-06-23-tupperlicious-chicken-adobo-and-spinach-laing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2013 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2013-06-23-tupperlicious-chicken-adobo-and-spinach-laing/</guid>
      <description>Chicken Adobo – this is the leftover adobo but more flavorful – more concentrated as a result of post-marination of the meat in its sauce.
 Chicken adobong tuyo   Spinach Laing – a special version of the traditional laing made of taro leaves!
 Lunchbox of rice and laing of spinach   We&amp;rsquo;ve got some dried dilis (anchovies) and this time sautéed in bagoong alamang (fermented shrimp paste).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beef Mechado</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/beef-mechado/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/beef-mechado/</guid>
      <description> Hearty beef stew slowly cooked in tomatoes, potatoes and vegetables.
INGREDIENTS:  500 grams beef cuts (fatty chunks are better) 3 ripe plump red tomatoes 2-3 medium potatoes 2 medium carrots 1 small jar tomato sauce 1 can button mushroom 2-3 cloves garlic 1 onion 1 cup water salt &amp;amp; black pepper to taste   Fresh chicken cuts    Fresh pechay    Bottle gourd gives the broth a sublte sweetness    It&amp;#39;s in the broth   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Sotanghon</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-sotanghon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-sotanghon/</guid>
      <description> Got colds or just feeling cold?? Here is a delicious way to get well and warm!
INGREDIENTS:  1 large chicken cut (leg-thigh) 250 grams sotanghon (vermicelli) 1-2 stalks celery (leaves included) 2 carrots 1&amp;frasl;2 head of cabbage 1 liter water 3 tablespon oil (canola or olive) 2 tablespoon patis (fish sauce) salt &amp;amp; black pepper to taste  For garnish:  green onions &amp;amp;toasted garlic chili oil   Also known as glass noodles   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mackerel Adobo</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/mackerel-adobo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/mackerel-adobo/</guid>
      <description> Quick and easy fish adobo dish of mackerel (typically galunggong). Delicious and good for your heart (mackerel is packed with omega-3 fatty acids).
INGREDIENTS  1 kg mackerel (or galunggong) 1 matchbox size ginger 3-4 cloves garlic 1 teaspoon sugar 1&amp;frasl;2 cup soy sauce 1&amp;frasl;4 cup vinegar freshly ground black pepper to taste green chilis for garnish  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Italian Carbonara</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/spaghetti-carbonara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/spaghetti-carbonara/</guid>
      <description> Easy to make delicious and creamy spaghetti carbonara dish. Kids love it and great for your next party!
INGREDIENTS:  500 grams Spaghetti 250 grams bacon, cut into strips 100 grams button mushroom 2-3 cloves garlic 1 onion 2 eggs cooking cream parsley salt &amp;amp; black pepper   Ingredients for making non-Italian carbonara   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork Bistek</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-bistek/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-bistek/</guid>
      <description> Pork chops marinated and braised in soy sauce, lemon juice, garlic and spices. Fried and topped with red onion rings
INGREDIENTS  1 kg pork cuts, pork chops or loin 2 lemons (or kalamansi) 2 red onions, sliced into rings 2-3 cloves garlic, crushed 1&amp;frasl;3 cup soy sauce 1 teaspoon sugar 1&amp;frasl;4 cup water black pepper to taste 1&amp;frasl;2 cup cooking oil for frying   Pork bistek with red onion rings   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tsitsarong Bituka</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicharon-bituka/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicharon-bituka/</guid>
      <description> Crispy and crunchy cracklings made from pork intestines. Classic pulutan or appetizer with matching hot spiced vinegar for dipping!
INGREDIENTS  1 kg pork intestines (washed very well) 1 liter water 1 tablespoon salt 1 tablespoon black peppercorns 3-4 bay leaves 3-4 cups cooking oil (for deep frying)  DIPPING SAUCE  3 tablespoons vinegar 1 clove garlic, crushed dash of salt and pepper   Crispy and crunchy cracklings with spiced vinegar dip   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Palitaw</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/palitaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/palitaw/</guid>
      <description> Classic Pinoy dessert of rice cakes topped with shredded coconut, sugar and sesame seeds.
INGREDIENTS  1 coconut, finely shredded 1 cup white sugar 30 grams sesame seeds, toasted 400 grams glutinous rice flour (galapong) 1 1&amp;frasl;2 cup water, for the dough 1 big pot of boiling water for cooking the rice cakes   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork Siomai</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2012-10-09-pork-siomai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2012-10-09-pork-siomai/</guid>
      <description>Siomai is the Philippines most popular dim sum. You can find it everywhere – from the tiniest streets to the mega malls. Siomai is easily the fastest merienda or even an ulam option. It has the perfect combination of pork and spicy dip (saw-sawan).
Siomai comes in different varieties and flavor mutations but we love the classic and simple pork siomai.
Ingredients  1&amp;frasl;2 kg ground pork 1 medium carrot, grated 1 medium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork Siomai</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-siomai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-siomai/</guid>
      <description>Siomai is the Philippines most popular dim sum. You can find it everywhere – from the tiniest streets to the mega malls. Siomai is easily the fastest merienda or even an ulam option. It has the perfect combination of pork and spicy dip (saw-sawan).
Siomai comes in different varieties and flavor mutations but we love the classic and simple pork siomai.
Ingredients  1&amp;frasl;2 kg ground pork 1 medium carrot, grated 1 medium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork Ribs Adobo</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-ribs-adobo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-ribs-adobo/</guid>
      <description> Pork ribs adobo with potatoes
INGREDIENTS  1 kg pork spare ribs, cut in small portions 2-3 medium potatoes, cut into cubes 1 head of garlic. peeled 2 bay leaves (dahon ng laurel) 1 tablespoon black peppercorns (pamintang buo) 1&amp;frasl;2 cup soy sauce 1 cup water 1&amp;frasl;2 cup cooking oil for frying the potatoes   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bopis</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/bopis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/bopis/</guid>
      <description> Pork innards braised in vinegar and spices
INGREDIENTS  1&amp;frasl;2 kg. lungs &amp;amp; 1&amp;frasl;2 kg. liver, finely chopped (pork or beef) 3 gloves garlic 1 big onion 1 cup radish, julienned cooking oil vinegar, salt and black pepper to taste   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ginisang Monggo</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/ginisang-monggo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/ginisang-monggo/</guid>
      <description> Mung beans cooked with pork belly strips, bitter gourd leaves
INGREDIENTS  250 grams monggo (mung beans) 1&amp;frasl;4 kg. pork belly, cut in to chunks 3 gloves garlic 1 big onion 2 medium tomatoes ampalaya leaves patis cooking oil 1.5 liters of water (use for pre-boiling the beans)   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beef Nilaga</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/beef-nilaga/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/beef-nilaga/</guid>
      <description> Slow cooked beef stew with vegetables
INGREDIENTS  1 kilo beef shank (leg portion) 3-4 medium potatoes 1 piece chinese cabbage (wombok) 1&amp;frasl;4 kg. green breens (bitsuelas) 1 large onion 1 cup chopped celery stalk 1&amp;frasl;2 tbsp. black pepper corns 3-4 tbsp. patis to taste spring onions for garnish   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish Sarciado</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/fish-sarciado/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/fish-sarciado/</guid>
      <description> Slow cooked beef stew with vegetables
INGREDIENTS  1 big fish cut into 3 pieces 3 large tomatoes 3 eggs 1 medium onion 5 gloves garlic 3 tbsp patis (fish sauce) 3 cups of water 1 siling berde (green chili) black pepper spring onion as garnish   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pancit Bihon</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pancit-bihon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pancit-bihon/</guid>
      <description> Pinoy noodles sauteéd with vegetable, pork belly and soy sauce
INGREDIENTS:  1&amp;frasl;2 piece dressed chicken (boiled, deboned and shredded; the stock use for cooking the noodles) 1&amp;frasl;2 kilo chicken liver 250 grams bihon (rice noodles) 1 medium carrots 100 grams green beans 2 stalks celery 1&amp;frasl;2 cup soy sauce 3 tbsp oyster sauce black pepper cooking oil   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grilled Fish</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/grilled-fish/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/grilled-fish/</guid>
      <description> Pinoy noodles sauteéd with vegetable, pork belly and soy sauce
INGREDIENTS:  1 big whole fish with scales (tilapia, bangus, we used dorada here) 1 large tomato 1 large onion 3 gloves garlic salt &amp;amp; black pepper   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beef Mushroom Broccoli</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/beef-mushroom-broccoli/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/beef-mushroom-broccoli/</guid>
      <description> Pinoy noodles sauteéd with vegetable, pork belly and soy sauce
Ingredients  1&amp;frasl;2 kg beef 1&amp;frasl;4 kg oyster mushroom 1&amp;frasl;2 kg broccoli 3 gloves garlic 1 onion 3 tbs. oyster sauce 1 tsp cornstarch 1&amp;frasl;2 cold water salt and pepper quail eggs for garnish   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork Belly Barbecue</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-barbeque/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-barbeque/</guid>
      <description> Pork belly strips marinated with spice soy sauce
Ingredients for the BBQ  3&amp;frasl;4 kilo pork belly strips 200 ml. barbecue marinade sauce 3 gloves garlic 1 big lemon black pepper  For the dip:  1&amp;frasl;4 cup vinegar 2 gloves garlic salt and pepper red hot chili  For basting:  Pork marinade cooking oil ketchup   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lumpiang Togue</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/lumpia-togue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/lumpia-togue/</guid>
      <description>Spring rolls stuffed with mung bean sprouts, tofu, pork and vegetables.
Ingredients  1&amp;frasl;4 kg. togue or mung bean sprouts 500 grams tofu 1&amp;frasl;4 kg. ground pork 1&amp;frasl;4 green beans (habituelas) 2 medium carrots 1 zayote 2 medium potatoes 3 gloves garlic and 1 medium onion 1 stalk of celery (kinchay) patis and black pepper lumpia wrapper  For the DIP:  vinegar garlic and onions salt and pepper chili pepper if you like it hot  Enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fideuá de Almejas</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-fideu%C3%A1-almejas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-fideu%C3%A1-almejas/</guid>
      <description>This is our lunch today. Simple recipe that is fillingly great! A favorite dish of mine served in Kaixo Taberna and here is my take on this tasty dish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkey Bleu d&#39;Auvergne</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-turkey-french-blue-cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:37:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-turkey-french-blue-cheese/</guid>
      <description>I used to tell myself that chicken breast and white onion are the good stuff. I would shop for it and make dishes out of it without even thinking about it. Until last weekend, I saw some turkey breast and remembered that I have red onions literally hanging around the kitchen. I realized that there are more textures and flavors from things we are not used to. Here is my proof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salmon &amp; Spinach</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-salmon-spinach/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:37:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-salmon-spinach/</guid>
      <description>If I ask my daughter, &amp;ldquo;What is your favorite fish?&amp;rdquo; In a heartbeat she will say, &amp;ldquo;Salmon!&amp;rdquo; Well, I cannot agree more. I like salmon too!
Here is a healthy recipe for the weekend if you have had too much land animal meat this week.
Ingredients  Salmon Spinach Onions Garlic Olive oil Salt &amp;amp; pepper Hierbas provenzales (albahaca, orégano, romero, tomillo, ajedrea &amp;amp; mejorana)  Procedure  Rub the salmon slice with the herbs, salt and pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spicy Hot Beef Broccoli</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-spicy-hot-beef-broccoli/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-spicy-hot-beef-broccoli/</guid>
      <description>I felt the need for some heat &amp;amp; action this weekend. That my friends is synonymous to stir-frying. Action-packed cooking from the chopping board to the wok.
Ingredients  Beef tenderloin, cut into strips Broccoli Red bell peppers Onions Garlic Soy sauce Cayenne pepper Olive oil &amp;amp; sesame oil Salt &amp;amp; pepper   Green little trees of health wonders   Procedure A wok is ideal for stir-frying but the regular pan will do but make sure it is smoky hot when you start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soy Mackerel</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-soy-mackerel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-soy-mackerel/</guid>
      <description>I miss Adobong galunggong, a popular and favorite Filipino dish. It&amp;rsquo;s fish braised in soy sauce, vinegar, ginger and garlic. It’s something we used to have weekly. Both words are iconic in the Philippines – adobo &amp;amp; galunggong &amp;hellip;
The closest fish I can get here in Madrid for this recipe is the caballa or the Atlantic Mackerel. Well, at least it is a mackerel.
Ingredients  Caballa (Mackerel) Garlic Mushrooms Pimiento de Padrón (green chili pepper) Soy sauce (naturally fermented) Lime juice or cider vinegar Ginger Laurel (bay leaf) Olive oil Hierbas provenzales (Albahaca, Orégano, Romero, Tomillo, Ajedrea &amp;amp; Mejorana) Salt &amp;amp; pepper Pimientos del piquillo, for garnish  Procedure  Cut the mackerel in halves then rub with hierbas provenzales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burger Rey</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-burger-rey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-burger-rey/</guid>
      <description>Last night while watching No Reservations Techniques episode, I told myself that I should make my own burger patty. Earlier today I&amp;rsquo;ve made my first attempt:
 Grilling patty to char   Not that bad I think. Here is the view from the back:
 Burger Rey, backview   Though I enjoyed it very much, there are still things that can be done to improve it. I will post the recipe in the next attempt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revuelto de Setas</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/2011/07/21/revuelto-setas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/2011/07/21/revuelto-setas/</guid>
      <description>Amazing symphony of flavors brought by the mix of five different mushrooms
 Frozen mixed mushrooms   Interesting fact: People who collect mushrooms for consumption are known as &amp;ldquo;mycophagists&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Sotanghon</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/2011/07/21/sotanghon-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/2011/07/21/sotanghon-chicken/</guid>
      <description>Springs officially starts today but really is still freezingly winter. The remedy – a hearty noodle soup perfect to warm you up, almost as good as a big hug.
Sotanghon are also known as glass noodles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tostada de Tomate</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/2011/07/21/tostada-tomate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/2011/07/21/tostada-tomate/</guid>
      <description>A refreshing breakfast to kick-start your day. Simple breakfast made great by fresh and top-quality ingredients – red ripe tomatoes, freshly-baked toasted bread and extra virgin olive oil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breakfast of Champions</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-breakfast-champion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:34:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-breakfast-champion/</guid>
      <description>Soft, moist and creamy eggs with cooked ham and queso tierno (soft cheese). I take my eggs seriously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filete de Ternera</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-filete-ternera-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:34:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-filete-ternera-/</guid>
      <description>Lunch at Kaixo with @twoixter a week ago. A filling meal for the heart and soul. Red meat with red wine is a classic.
The potato and mushroom stew was great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fishy Tortilla</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-fishy-tortilla/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-fishy-tortilla/</guid>
      <description>Tortilla española is the perfect brunch&amp;hellip; specially on Fridays.
A complete meal in itself, it has all the Go-Grow-Glow components.
Potatoes as carbs; eggs, and in this case, more protein from the mackerel; the rest of the ingredients as vitamin and mineral plus the healthy oils if you use virgin olive oil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bistek &amp; Chosuey</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-bistek-chopsuey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-bistek-chopsuey/</guid>
      <description>Combo rice toppings of soy braised beef, stir-fried vegs with chicken liver &amp;amp; gizzard.
Probably, one of the best-selling rice topping dishes sold in the Philippines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monggo &amp; Tamban</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-monggo-tamban/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-monggo-tamban/</guid>
      <description>Fried fish and ginisang mongo are married to each other. Delicious and nutritious mung bean stew cooked with pork belly strips and ampalaya. Paired with crispy fried sardine.
 Watch the Ginisang Monggo recipe video and cook-along with us!
Mung bean stew, rice and fried tamban</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corned Beef Soup</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/2011/07/21/corned-beef-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/2011/07/21/corned-beef-soup/</guid>
      <description>Hearty soup of corned beef, potato strips &amp;amp; cabbage. A breakfast to kick-start your day.
 Corned beef soup   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nilagang Baka &amp; Inihaw na Hito</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-beef-nilaga-broiled-catfish/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-beef-nilaga-broiled-catfish/</guid>
      <description>Cold and wet winter days? Cheer up and fire up with beef stew with green beans, chinese cabbage and potatoes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squash Blossoms Inabraw with Fried Milkfish</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-squash-blossoms-inabraw-fried-milkfish/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-squash-blossoms-inabraw-fried-milkfish/</guid>
      <description>The dish also contains long string beans (sitaw) with its young tops included, saluyot, and broiled milkfish. Inabraw is an Ilocano way of cooking veggie with fermented fish paste (bagoong isda) without any sauteing as opposed to pinakbet.
Mangantayon! Now you know how to say bon appétit in Iloko</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Brown Brunch</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-red-brown-brunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-red-brown-brunch/</guid>
      <description>Brunch is a combination of breakfast and lunch. The term is a portmanteau of breakfast and lunch. Often, it is a heavy meal meant to take the place of both breakfast and lunch.
A meal is not usually considered brunch if it is started before 10 o&amp;rsquo;clock in the morning, such meals would still be considered breakfast. Typically brunch is had at around 10AM, close to lunch time but still before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huevos Rotos con Espárragos</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-huevos-rotos-esparragos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-huevos-rotos-esparragos/</guid>
      <description>Here’s one of my all-time fave dish – Huevos Rotos which literally means “Broken Eggs.” It is not the typical scrambled eggs where you beat the egg whites &amp;amp; yolks together before you cook it.
Typically here in Madrid, the eggs are broken, literally when they serve it, in front of you!
 A dozen eggs on tray   Ingredients  2 Eggs Chorizo Iberico de Bellota (or any chorizo of your choosing) Asparagus (or any greens you like) Onions Garlics Olive oil Salt &amp;amp; Pepper Paprika &amp;amp; Parsley (for garnish)  Procedure  Sauté onion &amp;amp; garlic in olive oil Throw in the chorizo; let it sizzle until it change the color of the oil Add in the asparagus; sweat it and turn off stove Season with salt &amp;amp; pepper Now this is the part we “break” the eggs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>