<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Archives on The Ulampinoy Project</title>
    <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Archives on The Ulampinoy Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 20:59:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ulampinoy 2016</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/ulampinoy-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 20:59:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/ulampinoy-2016/</guid>
      <description>Masaya kaming ibalita sa inyo ang launch ng bagong disenyo ng Ulampinoy. Maraming improvements ang aming ginawa base sa mga feedback na tinanggap namin mula sa inyong lahat.
Ipinasya rin namin na i-publish ito sa wikang Tagalog. Nais naming i-share sa inyo ang mga recipe at iba pang bagay sa paraang mas personal na para bang panauhin namin kayo o panauhin ninyo kami sa inyong tahanan. Nakatitiyak kaming mas makulay ang ating kuwentuhan kung ito ay sa wikang Pilipino.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Ulampinoy</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/top-10-ulampinoy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 20:59:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/top-10-ulampinoy/</guid>
      <description>Tiyak na ang bawat isa ay may kani-kaniyang listahan ng mga paboritong ulam Pinoy. Narito ang ang aming top 10:
Adobong Manok Lahat malamang ay sasangayon na adobo ang #1 sa mga putaheng Pinoy, at puede sigurong ipalagay na adobong manok ang #1 sa lahat ng abodo dahil mas madaling makabili ng manok, kasi naman, mas mura ang manok kaysa baboy.
Adobong Baboy Ito sana ang #1 kaya lang mas mahal ang baboy kaysa manok!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pancit Bihon</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/pancit-bihon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 20:25:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/pancit-bihon/</guid>
      <description>Ano pa ang mas Pinoy sa pancit? Sa handaan o mga kainan, ang pancit ang isa sa mga pinaka-popular na pagkaing Filipino. Gaya ng adobo, napakaraming klase ng pancit. Pero ang pancit bihon ang isa sa aming paborito!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>La Bahia&#39;s Tasty Noodle Soup</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2016-01-21-la-bahia-noodle-soups/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 20:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2016-01-21-la-bahia-noodle-soups/</guid>
      <description>Two years ago, our friends recommended a really good Chinese restaurant that make some really tasty noodle soup. It was truly savoury!
 Bowls of tasty Chinese beef and seafoods noodle soup   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smashing Barcelona</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2016-01-05-smashing-barcelona/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 20:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2016-01-05-smashing-barcelona/</guid>
      <description>I was sent to Barcelona last October 2015 to attend the Smashing Conference. It was a great fun experience! Although it was my fifth visit, there are always new things and places to discover in Barcelona.
The conference venue was the magnificent Palau de la Música Catalana. The grandoise ceiling (shown above), stained-glass works and all the details are just splendid.
 Magnifecent Palau de la Música Catalana Facade and Terrace   During lunch breaks the attendees were encouraged to roam around the block close to the venue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burger Steak Rice</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-08-20-beef-burger-steak-rice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-08-20-beef-burger-steak-rice/</guid>
      <description>We love burgers! If you have meat between those buns why not with rice? And if it has to be a rice topping it needs to have sarsa (sauce). This is why burger steak is a perfect ulam!
The burger patties were prepared with a bit more of spices than the usual for hamburgers. It is loaded with garlic and a loads of ground black pepper. Adding up these will make it more connected as a rice topping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Togue Young Corn Stir-Fry</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-08-05-togue-young-corn-stir-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-08-05-togue-young-corn-stir-fry/</guid>
      <description>Hey there! We are back making and eating delicious home cooked meals. We have some upcoming news that will help spread the Ulampinoy love.
Meanwhile, enjoy the tasty and healthy bean sprout with young corn stir-fry. Makes a great take-away lunch. Try this: add a bit of kick with a dash of grounded cayenne pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Currently, cooking…</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-08-03-ulampinoy-dos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 23:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-08-03-ulampinoy-dos/</guid>
      <description>We are glad to launch today the fresh new look of UlamPinoy. We are currently redesigning the entire UlamPinoy site to make your visits to UlamPinoy fun and worthwhile an experience no matter if you are hunting for some tasty recipes or just feasting your eyes with our food adventure collections.
 Bowl of beef brisket noodle soup   As the title above suggests it is a work in progress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sinigang na Bangus</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-07-02-sinigang-bangus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2015 22:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-07-02-sinigang-bangus/</guid>
      <description>Milkfish or bangus is cooked in tamarind-based broth with onions, ginger, tomatoes, green chilis and pechay. Sinigang na Bangus is very popular because milkfish is the most common farmed fish in the Philippines. But not all bangus are equal! The most sought after is Dagupan Bangus in the province of Pangasinan.
 One whole tomato   Whether you are using the real sampaloc or the instant powder version, adding tomato to your sinigang upscale the broth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jamón Tumaca</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-07-01-tumaca/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-07-01-tumaca/</guid>
      <description>Typical Spaniard breakfast of toasted bread with jamón, tomato(finely chopped or grated) and extra-virgin olive oil.
 Pan tostada con tomate   Upscale it by adding a top layer of cured Spanish ham. When I said Spanish ham, I mean this:
 Charcutería, the one stop shop for everything pork goodness. All made possible with Spain&amp;rsquo;s super dry low air humidity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Churros &amp; Chocolate</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-06-26-churros-chocolate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2015 18:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-06-26-churros-chocolate/</guid>
      <description>Freshly made churros sprinkled with sugar and hot chocolate dip at the local churrería. It was both delightful eat and watch how it was made.
 La Churrera, the amazing churros machine   Kneading the dough, la masa, and the churros-making machine &amp;mdash; La Churrera
 Skillful skimming and draining   Churros ready! Skimmed and drained from the hot oil with the help of a steel rod
 Empty plastic jars for chocolate dip to go   Churrería Art – empty plastic jars of chocolate if you are buying for to go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monggo</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-06-26-monggo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2015 18:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-06-26-monggo/</guid>
      <description>Ginisang Monggo, the comfort food for all seasons. This I can have this every week. Paired with pritong isda or paksiw na isda is even better.
 Ginisang monggo on top of steamed rice   Quick tip: One of the essential step for the recipe is pre-cooking the mung beans by boiling until the skin of the beans separate. You don&amp;rsquo;t have to throw it.
 Pre-cooking to peel of skin   Check out our video recipe on how to cook Ginisang Monggo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kimchi</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-01-03-kimchi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2015 22:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2015-01-03-kimchi/</guid>
      <description>Spicy and sour are the flavors that could compliment any dish and enhance your appetite. Kimchi is both, spicy and sour.
It&amp;rsquo;s not easy to find a good kimchi here in Madrid. The bottled kimchi available at the Chinese store taste sweet! Really? Sweet kimchi? No thanks!
We found a proper Korean store in the Mercado de Maravillas in Cuatro Caminos. The shopkeeper is a Korean lady making her own kimchi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Misua and Patola</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2014-08-13-misua-patola/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2014-08-13-misua-patola/</guid>
      <description>Rice noodle (misua) soup with patola (luffa) and crispy pork belly strips
 Misua noodle soup with luffa   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garlic Pork Belly</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2013-10-23-garlic-pork-belly/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2013-10-23-garlic-pork-belly/</guid>
      <description>Got some pork belly in your fridge? Easy to make yet delicious crispy pork belly strips.
 Fresh pork belly strips and cloves of garlic   Ingredients  1 kg pork belly (cut into thick strips) 1 head of garlic (cruched, peeled and chooped) 1&amp;frasl;2 cup vinegar 1&amp;frasl;2 cup water salt and black pepper to taste  Great with some fresh green salads
Here&amp;rsquo;s the video on how to cook this delicious recipe:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Tinola</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2013-10-07-chicken-tinola/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2013-10-07-chicken-tinola/</guid>
      <description>Tinola will be at the top the list of ulam na may sabaw. It is chicken broth soup with upo (bottle gourd), pechay (Chinese cabbage) and ginger.
Ingredients  Whole chicken, cut into portions Upo (bottle gourd), 1 medium cut into chunks Pechay (Chinese cabbage, bok choi is great alternative), stalks and leaves separated Mild long green chilis Ginger, peeled and sliced Garlic Onions Cooking oil Patis (fish sauce) Salt to taste  If you can get free-range chicken, the broth will be many times tastier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chopsuey</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2013-09-30-chopsuey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2013-09-30-chopsuey/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re back in the kitchen for the 3rd Season of UlamPinoy! For our first episode we are cooking a very popular Filipino vegetable stir-fry recipe – Chopsuey.
 Golden brown pork belly strips in a wok   Fast and easy to cook. Fire up the wok, brown the pork belly until golden and crispy. Mix in the chicken livers. Sauté garlic and onions with the pork and livers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tupperlicious – Adobo &amp; Laing</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2013-06-23-tupperlicious-chicken-adobo-and-spinach-laing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2013 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2013-06-23-tupperlicious-chicken-adobo-and-spinach-laing/</guid>
      <description>Chicken Adobo – this is the leftover adobo but more flavorful – more concentrated as a result of post-marination of the meat in its sauce.
 Chicken adobong tuyo   Spinach Laing – a special version of the traditional laing made of taro leaves!
 Lunchbox of rice and laing of spinach   We&amp;rsquo;ve got some dried dilis (anchovies) and this time sautéed in bagoong alamang (fermented shrimp paste).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork Siomai</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2012-10-09-pork-siomai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2012-10-09-pork-siomai/</guid>
      <description>Siomai is the Philippines most popular dim sum. You can find it everywhere – from the tiniest streets to the mega malls. Siomai is easily the fastest merienda or even an ulam option. It has the perfect combination of pork and spicy dip (saw-sawan).
Siomai comes in different varieties and flavor mutations but we love the classic and simple pork siomai.
Ingredients  1&amp;frasl;2 kg ground pork 1 medium carrot, grated 1 medium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fideuá de Almejas</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-fideu%C3%A1-almejas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-fideu%C3%A1-almejas/</guid>
      <description>This is our lunch today. Simple recipe that is fillingly great! A favorite dish of mine served in Kaixo Taberna and here is my take on this tasty dish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkey Bleu d&#39;Auvergne</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-turkey-french-blue-cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:37:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-turkey-french-blue-cheese/</guid>
      <description>I used to tell myself that chicken breast and white onion are the good stuff. I would shop for it and make dishes out of it without even thinking about it. Until last weekend, I saw some turkey breast and remembered that I have red onions literally hanging around the kitchen. I realized that there are more textures and flavors from things we are not used to. Here is my proof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salmon &amp; Spinach</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-salmon-spinach/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:37:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-salmon-spinach/</guid>
      <description>If I ask my daughter, &amp;ldquo;What is your favorite fish?&amp;rdquo; In a heartbeat she will say, &amp;ldquo;Salmon!&amp;rdquo; Well, I cannot agree more. I like salmon too!
Here is a healthy recipe for the weekend if you have had too much land animal meat this week.
Ingredients  Salmon Spinach Onions Garlic Olive oil Salt &amp;amp; pepper Hierbas provenzales (albahaca, orégano, romero, tomillo, ajedrea &amp;amp; mejorana)  Procedure  Rub the salmon slice with the herbs, salt and pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spicy Hot Beef Broccoli</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-spicy-hot-beef-broccoli/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-spicy-hot-beef-broccoli/</guid>
      <description>I felt the need for some heat &amp;amp; action this weekend. That my friends is synonymous to stir-frying. Action-packed cooking from the chopping board to the wok.
Ingredients  Beef tenderloin, cut into strips Broccoli Red bell peppers Onions Garlic Soy sauce Cayenne pepper Olive oil &amp;amp; sesame oil Salt &amp;amp; pepper   Green little trees of health wonders   Procedure A wok is ideal for stir-frying but the regular pan will do but make sure it is smoky hot when you start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soy Mackerel</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-soy-mackerel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-soy-mackerel/</guid>
      <description>I miss Adobong galunggong, a popular and favorite Filipino dish. It&amp;rsquo;s fish braised in soy sauce, vinegar, ginger and garlic. It’s something we used to have weekly. Both words are iconic in the Philippines – adobo &amp;amp; galunggong &amp;hellip;
The closest fish I can get here in Madrid for this recipe is the caballa or the Atlantic Mackerel. Well, at least it is a mackerel.
Ingredients  Caballa (Mackerel) Garlic Mushrooms Pimiento de Padrón (green chili pepper) Soy sauce (naturally fermented) Lime juice or cider vinegar Ginger Laurel (bay leaf) Olive oil Hierbas provenzales (Albahaca, Orégano, Romero, Tomillo, Ajedrea &amp;amp; Mejorana) Salt &amp;amp; pepper Pimientos del piquillo, for garnish  Procedure  Cut the mackerel in halves then rub with hierbas provenzales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burger Rey</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-burger-rey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-burger-rey/</guid>
      <description>Last night while watching No Reservations Techniques episode, I told myself that I should make my own burger patty. Earlier today I&amp;rsquo;ve made my first attempt:
 Grilling patty to char   Not that bad I think. Here is the view from the back:
 Burger Rey, backview   Though I enjoyed it very much, there are still things that can be done to improve it. I will post the recipe in the next attempt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revuelto de Setas</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/2011/07/21/revuelto-setas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/2011/07/21/revuelto-setas/</guid>
      <description>Amazing symphony of flavors brought by the mix of five different mushrooms
 Frozen mixed mushrooms   Interesting fact: People who collect mushrooms for consumption are known as &amp;ldquo;mycophagists&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Sotanghon</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/2011/07/21/sotanghon-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/2011/07/21/sotanghon-chicken/</guid>
      <description>Springs officially starts today but really is still freezingly winter. The remedy – a hearty noodle soup perfect to warm you up, almost as good as a big hug.
Sotanghon are also known as glass noodles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tostada de Tomate</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/2011/07/21/tostada-tomate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/2011/07/21/tostada-tomate/</guid>
      <description>A refreshing breakfast to kick-start your day. Simple breakfast made great by fresh and top-quality ingredients – red ripe tomatoes, freshly-baked toasted bread and extra virgin olive oil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breakfast of Champions</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-breakfast-champion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:34:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-breakfast-champion/</guid>
      <description>Soft, moist and creamy eggs with cooked ham and queso tierno (soft cheese). I take my eggs seriously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filete de Ternera</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-filete-ternera-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:34:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-filete-ternera-/</guid>
      <description>Lunch at Kaixo with @twoixter a week ago. A filling meal for the heart and soul. Red meat with red wine is a classic.
The potato and mushroom stew was great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fishy Tortilla</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-fishy-tortilla/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-fishy-tortilla/</guid>
      <description>Tortilla española is the perfect brunch&amp;hellip; specially on Fridays.
A complete meal in itself, it has all the Go-Grow-Glow components.
Potatoes as carbs; eggs, and in this case, more protein from the mackerel; the rest of the ingredients as vitamin and mineral plus the healthy oils if you use virgin olive oil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bistek &amp; Chosuey</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-bistek-chopsuey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-bistek-chopsuey/</guid>
      <description>Combo rice toppings of soy braised beef, stir-fried vegs with chicken liver &amp;amp; gizzard.
Probably, one of the best-selling rice topping dishes sold in the Philippines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monggo &amp; Tamban</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-monggo-tamban/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-monggo-tamban/</guid>
      <description>Fried fish and ginisang mongo are married to each other. Delicious and nutritious mung bean stew cooked with pork belly strips and ampalaya. Paired with crispy fried sardine.
 Watch the Ginisang Monggo recipe video and cook-along with us!
Mung bean stew, rice and fried tamban</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corned Beef Soup</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/2011/07/21/corned-beef-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/2011/07/21/corned-beef-soup/</guid>
      <description>Hearty soup of corned beef, potato strips &amp;amp; cabbage. A breakfast to kick-start your day.
 Corned beef soup   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nilagang Baka &amp; Inihaw na Hito</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-beef-nilaga-broiled-catfish/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-beef-nilaga-broiled-catfish/</guid>
      <description>Cold and wet winter days? Cheer up and fire up with beef stew with green beans, chinese cabbage and potatoes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squash Blossoms Inabraw with Fried Milkfish</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-squash-blossoms-inabraw-fried-milkfish/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-squash-blossoms-inabraw-fried-milkfish/</guid>
      <description>The dish also contains long string beans (sitaw) with its young tops included, saluyot, and broiled milkfish. Inabraw is an Ilocano way of cooking veggie with fermented fish paste (bagoong isda) without any sauteing as opposed to pinakbet.
Mangantayon! Now you know how to say bon appétit in Iloko</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Brown Brunch</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-red-brown-brunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-red-brown-brunch/</guid>
      <description>Brunch is a combination of breakfast and lunch. The term is a portmanteau of breakfast and lunch. Often, it is a heavy meal meant to take the place of both breakfast and lunch.
A meal is not usually considered brunch if it is started before 10 o&amp;rsquo;clock in the morning, such meals would still be considered breakfast. Typically brunch is had at around 10AM, close to lunch time but still before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huevos Rotos con Espárragos</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-huevos-rotos-esparragos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/archive/2011-07-21-huevos-rotos-esparragos/</guid>
      <description>Here’s one of my all-time fave dish – Huevos Rotos which literally means “Broken Eggs.” It is not the typical scrambled eggs where you beat the egg whites &amp;amp; yolks together before you cook it.
Typically here in Madrid, the eggs are broken, literally when they serve it, in front of you!
 A dozen eggs on tray   Ingredients  2 Eggs Chorizo Iberico de Bellota (or any chorizo of your choosing) Asparagus (or any greens you like) Onions Garlics Olive oil Salt &amp;amp; Pepper Paprika &amp;amp; Parsley (for garnish)  Procedure  Sauté onion &amp;amp; garlic in olive oil Throw in the chorizo; let it sizzle until it change the color of the oil Add in the asparagus; sweat it and turn off stove Season with salt &amp;amp; pepper Now this is the part we “break” the eggs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>