<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Videos on The Ulampinoy Project</title>
    <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Videos on The Ulampinoy Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mongolian Beef</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/mongolian-beef/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/mongolian-beef/</guid>
      <description>Napakasarap at madaling lutuing beef stir-fry na saktong-sakto ulam.
BEEF at MARINADE:  1 kg. beef 2 buong bawang (12-15 butil) 4 tbs. Chinese cooking wine 3&amp;frasl;4 cornstarch 1 tb. baking soda 1 itlog pamintang durog 1 L cooking oil para sa pritong-lubog (deep-fry)  SAUCE:  1&amp;frasl;2 cup soy sauce 3 tbs. mirin 1&amp;frasl;4 cup sugar  GARNISH:  Green onion Roasted sesame seeds  Kain na! At huwag mag-atubiling mag-subscribe at paki-share ang ulam Pinoy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monggo</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/monggo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/monggo/</guid>
      <description> Ang monggo ay isang masarap na ulam na kadalasang may katambal na pritong isda. Karaniwang malunggay o talbos ng ampalaya ang sinasamang gulay. Napakasarap rin ng sasahugan pa ng tinapá at chicharon!
INGREDIENTS:  Monggo Liempo ng baboy Bawang Sibuyas Ampalaya Dahon ng spinach Patis at asin Siling haba Tubig  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beef Caldereta</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/beef-caldereta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/beef-caldereta/</guid>
      <description> Beef caldereta is one those dishes other than in the food shops that you can have only in a special meal (handaan).
INGREDIENTS:  Beef chunks Tomatoes, red and ripe Pineapple, chunks and juice from the can Liver spread, small can Potato and carrot Red and green sweet peppers Laurel leaves Salt and black pepper to taste Water  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Hot Spiced Vinegar</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/red-hot-spiced-vinegar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/red-hot-spiced-vinegar/</guid>
      <description> We&amp;rsquo;re back in the kitchen for the 3rd Season of UlamPinoy! For our first episode we are cooking a very popular Filipino vegetable stir-fry recipe – Chopsuey.
INGREDIENTS:  Beef chunks Tomatoes, red and ripe Pineapple, chunks and juice from the can Liver spread, small can Potato and carrot Red and green sweet peppers Laurel leaves Salt and black pepper to taste Water   Cooking chopsuey in a wok   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Afritada</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-afritada/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-afritada/</guid>
      <description>Easy to make one-pot chicken dish with vegetables. You can make a large batch and save some for your baon to work. It is a complete ulam where you have the sarsa for the rice and the main deal - chicken and vegetable.
Ingredients  Chicken Potatoes Carrots Red bell pepper Green bell pepper Tomatoes Garlic Onions Olive oil or canola Tomato sauce Patis (fish sauce) Salt and black pepper to taste   Cut into bite-size pieces   Procedure  Cut the chicken in medium portions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chopsuey</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chopsuey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chopsuey/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re back in the kitchen for the 3rd Season of UlamPinoy! For our first episode we are cooking a very popular Filipino vegetable stir-fry recipe – Chopsuey.
 Golden brown pork belly strips in a wok   Fast and easy to cook. Fire up the wok, brown the pork belly until golden and crispy. Mix in the chicken livers. Sauté garlic and onions with the pork and livers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Stir-fry</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-stir-fry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-stir-fry/</guid>
      <description> Fire up your wok and cook along with our easy to make chicken and vegetable stir-fry.
INGREDIENTS:  Chicken Vegetables   Red bell pepper on chopping board   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Sopas</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-sopas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-sopas/</guid>
      <description> Chicken and elbow macaroni soup cooked in milk as base with carrots, cabbage and sausage. Perfect comfort food during the cold winter days!
INGREDIENTS:  Chicken Elbow macaroni   Chicken Sopas served hot   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Crispy Pork Belly</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/super-crispy-pork-belly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/super-crispy-pork-belly/</guid>
      <description> Chicken and elbow macaroni soup cooked in milk as base with carrots, cabbage and sausage. Perfect comfort food during the cold winter days!
INGREDIENTS:  Beef chunks Tomatoes, red and ripe Pineapple, chunks and juice from the can Liver spread, small can Potato and carrot Red and green sweet peppers Laurel leaves Salt and black pepper to taste Water   Salt liberally the pork belly    Pork crackling with dip   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ginisang Green Beans</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/ginisang-green-beans/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/ginisang-green-beans/</guid>
      <description> Easy to cook sautéed green beans with crispy pork belly
INGREDIENTS:  Green beans Pork belly   Sauté the pork belly until golden brown    Covering while simmering tenderize the green beans faster   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revuelto de Setas</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/revuelto-setas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/revuelto-setas/</guid>
      <description> Simple to make Spanish omelette of mixed mushrooms and chorizo
INGREDIENTS:  Mushroom mix Eggs Spanish chorizo   Eggs dancing on a tray   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Squid Adobo</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/squid-adobo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/squid-adobo/</guid>
      <description>Fresh squids cooked adobo style! We love it very much and it really shows – this is the second video of Adobong Pusit
 Preserve the ink duct if you buy the squid fresh or you can always use squid/cuttlefish ink sold in packets. Most supermarkets here in Madrid sell &amp;ldquo;tinta de sepia/calamar&amp;rdquo;
 Cuttlefish ink packet   Cook the squid at high heat in less time until it gets tender and add the vinegar for last.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ginataang Kalabasa</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/ginataang-kalabasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/ginataang-kalabasa/</guid>
      <description> Squash, string beans and live crabs cooked in spiced coconut milk. Savoury and spicy!
INGREDIENTS:  Squash String beans Crabs   Long string beans bundle    Fresh kalabasa    Fresh from the market live crab   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crispy Garlic Pork Belly</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/garlic-pork-belly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/garlic-pork-belly/</guid>
      <description> Crispy, golden and garlicky pork belly
INGREDIENTS:  1 kg pork belly (cut into thick strips) 1 head of garlic (cruched, peeled and chooped) 1&amp;frasl;2 cup vinegar 1&amp;frasl;2 cup water salt and black pepper to taste   Fresh pork belly and handful of garlic cloves    Crispy garlic loaded liempo   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sinigang na Hipon at Isda</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/sinigang-hipon-isda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/sinigang-hipon-isda/</guid>
      <description> Seafoods stew of fish, shrimp, talbos ng kamote (sweet potato young leaves), tomatoes, ginger, mild green chili and onions.
INGREDIENTS:  1 kg pork belly (cut into thick strips) 1 head of garlic (cruched, peeled and chooped) 1&amp;frasl;2 cup vinegar 1&amp;frasl;2 cup water salt and black pepper to taste   Fresh sweet potato tops    Fresh sweet potato tops    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Tinola</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-tinola/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-tinola/</guid>
      <description> Savory and revitalizing chicken broth soup spiced with ginger, garlic, onions and with bottle gourd and pechay.
INGREDIENTS:  Whole chicken, 1 pc. cut into portions Upo (bottle gourd), 1 medium cut into chunks Pechay (Chinese cabbage, bok choi is great alternative), stalks and leaves separated Mild long green chilis Ginger, peeled and sliced Garlic Onions Cooking oil Patis (fish sauce) Salt to taste   Fresh chicken cuts    Fresh pechay    Bottle gourd gives the broth a sublte sweetness    It&amp;#39;s in the broth   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beef Mechado</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/beef-mechado/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/beef-mechado/</guid>
      <description> Hearty beef stew slowly cooked in tomatoes, potatoes and vegetables.
INGREDIENTS:  500 grams beef cuts (fatty chunks are better) 3 ripe plump red tomatoes 2-3 medium potatoes 2 medium carrots 1 small jar tomato sauce 1 can button mushroom 2-3 cloves garlic 1 onion 1 cup water salt &amp;amp; black pepper to taste   Fresh chicken cuts    Fresh pechay    Bottle gourd gives the broth a sublte sweetness    It&amp;#39;s in the broth   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Sotanghon</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-sotanghon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-sotanghon/</guid>
      <description> Got colds or just feeling cold?? Here is a delicious way to get well and warm!
INGREDIENTS:  1 large chicken cut (leg-thigh) 250 grams sotanghon (vermicelli) 1-2 stalks celery (leaves included) 2 carrots 1&amp;frasl;2 head of cabbage 1 liter water 3 tablespon oil (canola or olive) 2 tablespoon patis (fish sauce) salt &amp;amp; black pepper to taste  For garnish:  green onions &amp;amp;toasted garlic chili oil   Also known as glass noodles   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mackerel Adobo</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/mackerel-adobo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/mackerel-adobo/</guid>
      <description> Quick and easy fish adobo dish of mackerel (typically galunggong). Delicious and good for your heart (mackerel is packed with omega-3 fatty acids).
INGREDIENTS  1 kg mackerel (or galunggong) 1 matchbox size ginger 3-4 cloves garlic 1 teaspoon sugar 1&amp;frasl;2 cup soy sauce 1&amp;frasl;4 cup vinegar freshly ground black pepper to taste green chilis for garnish  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-Italian Carbonara</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/spaghetti-carbonara/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/spaghetti-carbonara/</guid>
      <description> Easy to make delicious and creamy spaghetti carbonara dish. Kids love it and great for your next party!
INGREDIENTS:  500 grams Spaghetti 250 grams bacon, cut into strips 100 grams button mushroom 2-3 cloves garlic 1 onion 2 eggs cooking cream parsley salt &amp;amp; black pepper   Ingredients for making non-Italian carbonara   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork Bistek</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-bistek/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-bistek/</guid>
      <description> Pork chops marinated and braised in soy sauce, lemon juice, garlic and spices. Fried and topped with red onion rings
INGREDIENTS  1 kg pork cuts, pork chops or loin 2 lemons (or kalamansi) 2 red onions, sliced into rings 2-3 cloves garlic, crushed 1&amp;frasl;3 cup soy sauce 1 teaspoon sugar 1&amp;frasl;4 cup water black pepper to taste 1&amp;frasl;2 cup cooking oil for frying   Pork bistek with red onion rings   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tsitsarong Bituka</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicharon-bituka/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicharon-bituka/</guid>
      <description> Crispy and crunchy cracklings made from pork intestines. Classic pulutan or appetizer with matching hot spiced vinegar for dipping!
INGREDIENTS  1 kg pork intestines (washed very well) 1 liter water 1 tablespoon salt 1 tablespoon black peppercorns 3-4 bay leaves 3-4 cups cooking oil (for deep frying)  DIPPING SAUCE  3 tablespoons vinegar 1 clove garlic, crushed dash of salt and pepper   Crispy and crunchy cracklings with spiced vinegar dip   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Palitaw</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/palitaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/palitaw/</guid>
      <description> Classic Pinoy dessert of rice cakes topped with shredded coconut, sugar and sesame seeds.
INGREDIENTS  1 coconut, finely shredded 1 cup white sugar 30 grams sesame seeds, toasted 400 grams glutinous rice flour (galapong) 1 1&amp;frasl;2 cup water, for the dough 1 big pot of boiling water for cooking the rice cakes   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork Siomai</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-siomai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-siomai/</guid>
      <description>Siomai is the Philippines most popular dim sum. You can find it everywhere – from the tiniest streets to the mega malls. Siomai is easily the fastest merienda or even an ulam option. It has the perfect combination of pork and spicy dip (saw-sawan).
Siomai comes in different varieties and flavor mutations but we love the classic and simple pork siomai.
Ingredients  1&amp;frasl;2 kg ground pork 1 medium carrot, grated 1 medium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork Ribs Adobo</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-ribs-adobo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-ribs-adobo/</guid>
      <description> Pork ribs adobo with potatoes
INGREDIENTS  1 kg pork spare ribs, cut in small portions 2-3 medium potatoes, cut into cubes 1 head of garlic. peeled 2 bay leaves (dahon ng laurel) 1 tablespoon black peppercorns (pamintang buo) 1&amp;frasl;2 cup soy sauce 1 cup water 1&amp;frasl;2 cup cooking oil for frying the potatoes   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bopis</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/bopis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/bopis/</guid>
      <description> Pork innards braised in vinegar and spices
INGREDIENTS  1&amp;frasl;2 kg. lungs &amp;amp; 1&amp;frasl;2 kg. liver, finely chopped (pork or beef) 3 gloves garlic 1 big onion 1 cup radish, julienned cooking oil vinegar, salt and black pepper to taste   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ginisang Monggo</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/ginisang-monggo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/ginisang-monggo/</guid>
      <description> Mung beans cooked with pork belly strips, bitter gourd leaves
INGREDIENTS  250 grams monggo (mung beans) 1&amp;frasl;4 kg. pork belly, cut in to chunks 3 gloves garlic 1 big onion 2 medium tomatoes ampalaya leaves patis cooking oil 1.5 liters of water (use for pre-boiling the beans)   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beef Nilaga</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/beef-nilaga/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/beef-nilaga/</guid>
      <description> Slow cooked beef stew with vegetables
INGREDIENTS  1 kilo beef shank (leg portion) 3-4 medium potatoes 1 piece chinese cabbage (wombok) 1&amp;frasl;4 kg. green breens (bitsuelas) 1 large onion 1 cup chopped celery stalk 1&amp;frasl;2 tbsp. black pepper corns 3-4 tbsp. patis to taste spring onions for garnish   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish Sarciado</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/fish-sarciado/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/fish-sarciado/</guid>
      <description> Slow cooked beef stew with vegetables
INGREDIENTS  1 big fish cut into 3 pieces 3 large tomatoes 3 eggs 1 medium onion 5 gloves garlic 3 tbsp patis (fish sauce) 3 cups of water 1 siling berde (green chili) black pepper spring onion as garnish   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pancit Bihon</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pancit-bihon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pancit-bihon/</guid>
      <description> Pinoy noodles sauteéd with vegetable, pork belly and soy sauce
INGREDIENTS:  1&amp;frasl;2 piece dressed chicken (boiled, deboned and shredded; the stock use for cooking the noodles) 1&amp;frasl;2 kilo chicken liver 250 grams bihon (rice noodles) 1 medium carrots 100 grams green beans 2 stalks celery 1&amp;frasl;2 cup soy sauce 3 tbsp oyster sauce black pepper cooking oil   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grilled Fish</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/grilled-fish/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/grilled-fish/</guid>
      <description> Pinoy noodles sauteéd with vegetable, pork belly and soy sauce
INGREDIENTS:  1 big whole fish with scales (tilapia, bangus, we used dorada here) 1 large tomato 1 large onion 3 gloves garlic salt &amp;amp; black pepper   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beef Mushroom Broccoli</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/beef-mushroom-broccoli/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/beef-mushroom-broccoli/</guid>
      <description> Pinoy noodles sauteéd with vegetable, pork belly and soy sauce
Ingredients  1&amp;frasl;2 kg beef 1&amp;frasl;4 kg oyster mushroom 1&amp;frasl;2 kg broccoli 3 gloves garlic 1 onion 3 tbs. oyster sauce 1 tsp cornstarch 1&amp;frasl;2 cold water salt and pepper quail eggs for garnish   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork Belly Barbecue</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-barbeque/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-barbeque/</guid>
      <description> Pork belly strips marinated with spice soy sauce
Ingredients for the BBQ  3&amp;frasl;4 kilo pork belly strips 200 ml. barbecue marinade sauce 3 gloves garlic 1 big lemon black pepper  For the dip:  1&amp;frasl;4 cup vinegar 2 gloves garlic salt and pepper red hot chili  For basting:  Pork marinade cooking oil ketchup   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lumpiang Togue</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/lumpia-togue/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/lumpia-togue/</guid>
      <description>Spring rolls stuffed with mung bean sprouts, tofu, pork and vegetables.
Ingredients  1&amp;frasl;4 kg. togue or mung bean sprouts 500 grams tofu 1&amp;frasl;4 kg. ground pork 1&amp;frasl;4 green beans (habituelas) 2 medium carrots 1 zayote 2 medium potatoes 3 gloves garlic and 1 medium onion 1 stalk of celery (kinchay) patis and black pepper lumpia wrapper  For the DIP:  vinegar garlic and onions salt and pepper chili pepper if you like it hot  Enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>