<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Video Beef on The Ulampinoy Project</title>
    <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/categories/video-beef/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Video Beef on The Ulampinoy Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.ulampinoy.com/categories/video-beef/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Beef Caldereta</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/beef-caldereta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/beef-caldereta/</guid>
      <description> Beef caldereta is one those dishes other than in the food shops that you can have only in a special meal (handaan).
INGREDIENTS:  Beef chunks Tomatoes, red and ripe Pineapple, chunks and juice from the can Liver spread, small can Potato and carrot Red and green sweet peppers Laurel leaves Salt and black pepper to taste Water  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beef Mechado</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/beef-mechado/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/beef-mechado/</guid>
      <description> Hearty beef stew slowly cooked in tomatoes, potatoes and vegetables.
INGREDIENTS:  500 grams beef cuts (fatty chunks are better) 3 ripe plump red tomatoes 2-3 medium potatoes 2 medium carrots 1 small jar tomato sauce 1 can button mushroom 2-3 cloves garlic 1 onion 1 cup water salt &amp;amp; black pepper to taste   Fresh chicken cuts    Fresh pechay    Bottle gourd gives the broth a sublte sweetness    It&amp;#39;s in the broth   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Sotanghon</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-sotanghon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicken-sotanghon/</guid>
      <description> Got colds or just feeling cold?? Here is a delicious way to get well and warm!
INGREDIENTS:  1 large chicken cut (leg-thigh) 250 grams sotanghon (vermicelli) 1-2 stalks celery (leaves included) 2 carrots 1&amp;frasl;2 head of cabbage 1 liter water 3 tablespon oil (canola or olive) 2 tablespoon patis (fish sauce) salt &amp;amp; black pepper to taste  For garnish:  green onions &amp;amp;toasted garlic chili oil   Also known as glass noodles   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>