<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Video Pork on The Ulampinoy Project</title>
    <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/categories/video-pork/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Video Pork on The Ulampinoy Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.ulampinoy.com/categories/video-pork/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Crispy Pork Belly</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/super-crispy-pork-belly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/super-crispy-pork-belly/</guid>
      <description> Chicken and elbow macaroni soup cooked in milk as base with carrots, cabbage and sausage. Perfect comfort food during the cold winter days!
INGREDIENTS:  Beef chunks Tomatoes, red and ripe Pineapple, chunks and juice from the can Liver spread, small can Potato and carrot Red and green sweet peppers Laurel leaves Salt and black pepper to taste Water   Salt liberally the pork belly    Pork crackling with dip   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork Bistek</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-bistek/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/pork-bistek/</guid>
      <description> Pork chops marinated and braised in soy sauce, lemon juice, garlic and spices. Fried and topped with red onion rings
INGREDIENTS  1 kg pork cuts, pork chops or loin 2 lemons (or kalamansi) 2 red onions, sliced into rings 2-3 cloves garlic, crushed 1&amp;frasl;3 cup soy sauce 1 teaspoon sugar 1&amp;frasl;4 cup water black pepper to taste 1&amp;frasl;2 cup cooking oil for frying   Pork bistek with red onion rings   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tsitsarong Bituka</title>
      <link>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicharon-bituka/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ulampinoy.com/video/chicharon-bituka/</guid>
      <description> Crispy and crunchy cracklings made from pork intestines. Classic pulutan or appetizer with matching hot spiced vinegar for dipping!
INGREDIENTS  1 kg pork intestines (washed very well) 1 liter water 1 tablespoon salt 1 tablespoon black peppercorns 3-4 bay leaves 3-4 cups cooking oil (for deep frying)  DIPPING SAUCE  3 tablespoons vinegar 1 clove garlic, crushed dash of salt and pepper   Crispy and crunchy cracklings with spiced vinegar dip   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>